

## PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

User research
Usability testing
User personas
Wireframing
High-Fi Mock-ups
Pendo
Miro
Figma
Adobe Photoshop Suite
VS Code
Style guides /design systems
HTML and CSS engineering
Basic JavaScript coding
React JavaScript Hooks

### CONTACT

P: 615-627-8548

E: sageklein@gmail.com W: www.sageklein.com L: linkedin.com/in/sage-klein

# SAGE KLEIN

UI/UX DESIGN

#### ABOUT

I love waking up and spending my day learning new things and tackling challenging problems. With 2+ years in the UI/UX Design field I have found that having, empathy, curiosity and a strong aesthetic sense of how features and functions fit together are the most important aspects of creating beautiful designs. UI is best when it is intuitive and UX is best when it is delightful.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## PRODUCT DESIGNER

HealthStream | April 2021 - Present

- Plan and conduct user research activities, surveys, interviews, usability studies, analytics reports, pilot testing etc., to guide product design and ongoing improvements
- Create high-fi mockups, prototypes and workflow diagrams as needed; ensuring design aligns with established patterns, user validation and research
- Improve existing products and functionality to create a better user experience; update processes and workflows to accommodate changing business needs
- Develop and organize design components for sharing across the organization

## TEACHING ASSISTANT

Nashville Software School | May 2020 - April 2021

- Taught application development through group and individual projects reflecting real world problems
- Taught tools such as Figma, Miro, Sketch, XD, flowchart, and diagramming tools
- Taught application styling with CSS and SASS Frameworks, Bootstrap, Siminatic UI and various style libraries

## **EDUCATION**

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER & UI UX DESIGNER

Nashville Software School | 2019 - 2020

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN INTERDISCIPLINARY STUDIES

Middle Tennessee State University | 2012 - 2014

**GPA 4.0**